Soviet Union Unregistered Baptists Subject Files, Inclusive: 1948-2011, undated, Bulk: 1960-1989
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Samizdat, 1961-1987, 2011, undated; 2
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 1, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 5-6, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 3-4, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 6, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 4-5, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bratskii listok, No. 2, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 1, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 1: Extra copies, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 1: Translated documents, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 2, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 2. Extra Copy, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 3, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 4, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 5, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 6, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 7, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 7: Translated documents, notes, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 8, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 9, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 9: Translated documents, notes, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 10, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 10. Notes, Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 11, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 11: Translated documents, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 12, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 12: Extra copies, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 13, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 13. Notes, Reports, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 14, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 14: Extra copies, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 15, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 15: Extra copies, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 16, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 16: Extra copies, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 17, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 17: Extra copies, translated documents, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 18, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 18: Extra copies, translated documents, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 19, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 20, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 20: Translated documents, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 21, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 21: Extra copies, translated documents, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 22, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 22: Translated documents, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 23, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 23: Translated documents, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 24, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 24: Extra copies, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 24: Notes of a Believer, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 24-25, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 25, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 25: Translated documents, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 26, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 26: Translated documents, notes, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 27, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 27: Extra copies, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 27: Extra copies, translated documents, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 28, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 28: Extra copies, notes, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 28: Extra copies, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 29, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 30, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 30: Extra copies, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 31, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 31: Extra copy, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 31: Translated documents, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 32, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 32, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 33, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 33: Extra copies; translated documents, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 34, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 34: Extra copies, notes, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 35, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 36, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 36: Extra copies, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 36: Extra copies, translated documents, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 37, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 37: Extra copies, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 37: Extra copies, translated documents, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 38, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 38: Extra copies, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 39, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 39: Extra copies, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 40, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 40: Translated documents, notes, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 41, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 42, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 42: Extra copies; translated documents, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 43, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 43 (Part II), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 44, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 44: Extra copies, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 45, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 45: Translated documents, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 46, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 46: Extra copies, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 46: Extra copies, translated documents, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 47, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 47: Extra copies, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 48, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 48, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 49, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 50, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 51, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 51: Extra copies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 51: Extra copies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 52, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 52: Extra copies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 53, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, Extraordinary Issue, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 54, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 54: Extra copies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 55, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 55: Extra copies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 56, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 56: Extra copies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 56: Translated documents, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 57, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 58, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 59, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 60, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 61, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 62, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 63, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Unregistered Baptist Church. Samizdat Publication. Bulletin of the Council of Relatives of Evangelical Christians and Baptists Prisoners, No. 64, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 22)